1327 Camino Linda Drive, San Marcos CA, 92078

(760)-586-5318

OBJECTIVE

Clinical Laboratory Associate with 4 years of BioPharma related experience, seeking an opportunity to utilize my attention to detail, interpersonal skills, and adaptability to rapid changing work environments; allowing me to grow personally and professionally within a research oriented community.

SKILLS

- Experience following SOPs in a GMP/GCP/GLP/CLIA regulated environment
- Pre-analytical processing of specimens
- Strong attention to detail
- Familiar with LabVantage LIMS
- Data entry
- Detailed documentation
- Organized
- Adaptable to fast paced-environments
- Knowledge of electrophoresis, DNA mini isolation, cell culturing, and protein purification.

EDUCATION

Biomanufacturing Major, Mira Costa College, Oceanside, CA,

2016 - Present

46 units completed for A.S. in Biomanufacturing, expected date of graduation May 2022

High School Diploma, Murrieta Valley High School, Murrieta

2012-2016

EXPERIENCE

Clinical Laboratory Associate 1, Navigate Biopharma Services Inc., Carlsbad, California

03/2020- Present

- Handling, processing, transporting, archiving, and storing patient specimens
- Perform quality control review of data in a laboratory information management system (LIMS).
- Reagent preparation (Freezing media).
- Identify problems related to specimen processing and immediately notify line management
- Document quality control activities, instrument maintenance, and other required laboratory functions
- Sample tracking and storage procedures for all incoming and specimens.
- Ensure change requests are properly initiated, completed, and approved prior to the use of the assay, system, instrument, software, etc. being changed

Laboratory Assistant, Navigate Biopharma Services Inc., Carlsbad, California

10/2018-03/2020

- Checking patient specimens into and out of the archival storage system
- Organization and maintenance of slide storage room
- Maintenance of archive records, fulfilling specimen returns
- Supply ordering and restocking

Material Handler, Navigate Biopharma Services Inc., Carlsbad, California

01/2017-10/2018

- Responsible for shipping and receiving testing materials
- Maintained clear lines of communication between the business and external shipping partners
- Triaged errors in received goods
- Maintained accurate purchasing and inventory information in Great Plains, SAP, PMIS, and Excel

Child Care Provider, Promise Lutheran Church, Murrieta, California

07/2016-02/2017